<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E-manual</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="result_text">Results displayed here</string>
    <string name="main">E-manual</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">splash</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="text_content">Check the Parking Brake Warning Light by placing the ignition switch to the ON position (do not start the engine). This light will be illuminated when the parking brake is applied with the ignition switch in the START or ON position. Before driving, be sure the parking brake is released and the Brake Warning Light is OFF. If the Parking Brake Warning Light remains on after the parking brake is released while engine is running, there may be a malfunction in the brake system. Immediate attention is necessary. If at all possible, cease driving the vehicle immediately. If that is not possible, use extreme caution while operating the vehicle and only continue to drive the vehicle until you can reach a safe location. </string>
    <string name="notebrake">Driving the vehicle with a warning light on is dangerous. If the brake warning light remains on, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer</string>
    <string name="user_name">Parking Brake</string>
    <string name="abs">This warning light illuminates if the ignition switch is placed in the ON position and goes off after approximately 3 seconds if the system is operating normally. If the ABS warning light remains on, comes on while driving, or does not come on when the ignition switch is placed in the ON position, this indicates that the ABS may have malfunctioned. If this occurs, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer. The normal braking system will still be operational, but without the assistance of the anti-lock brake system.</string>
    <string name="noteabs">An Anti-Lock Braking System (ABS) will not prevent accidents due to improper or dangerous driving maneuvers. Even though vehicle control is improved during emergency braking, always maintain a safe distance between you and objects ahead of you. Vehicle speeds should always be reduced during extreme road conditions. The braking distance for cars equipped with ABS may be longer than for those without these systems in the following road conditions. • Drive your vehicle at reduced speeds during the following conditions: • Rough, gravel or snow-covered roads. • On roads where the road surface is pitted or has different surface height. • Tire chains are installed on your vehicle. The safety features of an ABS equipped vehicle should not be tested by high speed driving or cornering. This could endanger the safety of yourself or others.</string>
    <string name="airbag">Your vehicle is equipped with a Supplemental Restraint System (SRS) and lap/shoulder belts at both the driver and passenger seating positions. The SRS consists of air bags which are located in the center of the steering wheel and the passengers side front panel pad above the glove box. The air bags are labeled with the letters AIR BAG embossed on the pad covers.</string>
    <string name="noteair">To reduce the risk of an air bag deploying unexpectedly and causing serious injury or death:
 • Do not hit or allow any objects to impact the locations where air bags or sensors are installed.
• Do not perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. If the location or angle of the sensors is altered, the air bags may deploy when they should not or may not deploy when they should.
• Do not install bumper guards or replace the bumper with a non-genuine part. This may adversely affect the collision and air bag deployment performance.
• We recommend that all repairs are conducted by an authorized dealer.
</string>
    <string name="battery">This warning light indicates a malfunction of either the generator or electrical charging system. If the warning light illuminates while the vehicle is in motion: 1. Drive to the nearest safe location. 2. With the engine off, check the generator drive belt for looseness or breakage. 3. If the belt is adjusted properly, a problem exists somewhere in the electrical charging system. We recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer.</string>
    <string name="check">This indicator is part of the Engine Control System which monitors various emission control system components. If this indicator illuminates while driving, it indicates that a potential malfunction has been detected somewhere in the emission control system. This indicator will also illuminates when the ignition switch is placed in the ON position, and will go off in a few seconds after the engine is started. If it illuminates while driving, or does not illuminate when the ignition switch is placed in the ON position, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized HYUNDAI dealer. Generally, your vehicle will continue to be drivable, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer.</string>
    <string name="parking">This indicator illuminates when the parking (position) light are on.</string>
    <string name="door">This warning light illuminates when a door is not closed securely. The light comes on when a door is opened regardless of the ignition switch position. When doors are unlocked by the remote key, the light comes on for approximately 30 seconds as long as a door is not opened. The light goes out gradually after approximately 30 seconds if the door is closed. However, if the ignition switch is ON or all doors are locked, the light will go out immediately. If a door is opened with the ignition switch in the ACC or LOCK/OFF position, the light stays on for about 20 minutes. However, if a door is opened with the ignition switch in the ON position, the light stays on continuously.</string>
    <string name="fog">This indicator illuminates when the front fog lights are ON. Front  Fog lights are used to provide improved visibility and avoid accidents when visibility is poor due to fog, rain or snow etc. The fog lights will turn on when fog light switch (1) is turned to the ON position after the parking light is turned on. To turn off the fog lights, turn the switch to the OFF position</string>
    <string name="notefog">When in operation, the fog lights consume large amounts of vehicle electrical power. Only use the fog lights when visibility is poor or unnecessary battery and generator drain could occur.</string>
    <string name="highbeam">This indicator illuminates when the headlights are on and in the high beam position or when the turn signal lever is pulled into the Flash-to-Pass position</string>
    <string name="oil">This warning light indicates the engine oil pressure is low. If the warning light illuminates while driving: 1. Drive safely to the side of the road and stop. 2. With the engine off, check the engine oil level. If the level is low, add oil as required. If the warning light remains on after adding oil or if oil is not available, we recommend that you call an authorized dealer.</string>
    <string name="noteoil">If the oil pressure warning light stays on while the engine is running, serious engine damage may result. The oil pressure warning light comes on whenever there is insufficient oil pressure. In normal operation, it should come on when the ignition switch is turned on, then goes off when the engine starts. If the oil pressure warning light stays on while the engine is running, there is a serious malfunction. If this happens, stop the vehicle as soon as it is safe to do so, turn off the engine and check the oil level. If the oil level is low, fill the engine oil to the proper level and start the engine again. If the light stays on with the engine running, turn the engine off immediately. In any instance where the oil light stays on when the engine is running, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer</string>
    <string name="steering">This indicator light illuminates after the ignition key is placed in the ON position and then it will go off when the engine starts. This light also comes on when the EPS has malfunctioned. If it comes on while driving, we recommend that the system be inspected by an authorized dealer.</string>
    <string name="notesteering">• Never adjust the angle and height of the steering wheel while driving. You may lose steering control and cause severe personal injury, death or accidents. • After adjusting, push the steering wheel both up and down to be certain it is locked in position.</string>
    <string name="seatbelt">As a reminder to the driver, the seat belt warning light will blink for approximately 6 seconds each time you place the ignition switch in the ON position regardless of belt fastening. If the driver’s seat belt is unfastened after the ignition switch is placed in the ON position, the seat belt warning light blinks again for approximately 6 seconds. If the drivers seat belt is not fastened when the ignition switch is placed in the ON position or if it is unfastened after the ignition switch is placed in the ON position, the seat belt warning chime will sound for approximately 6 seconds. At this time, if the seat belt is fastened, the chime will stop at once</string>
    <string name="noteseat">•	Never wear the shoulder belt under your arm or behind your back. An improperly positioned shoulder belt can cause serious injuries in a crash. The shoulder belt should be positioned midway over your shoulder across your collarbone.
•	Avoid wearing twisted seat belts. A twisted seat belt will not protect you properly in an accident. Be sure the belt webbing is straight and not twisted.
•	Be careful not to damage the belt webbing or hardware. If the belt webbing or hardware is damaged, replace it.
</string>
    <string name="security">This indicator illuminates when the immobilizer key is inserted and turned to the ON position to start the engine. At this time, you can start the engine. The light goes off after the engine is running. If this light blinks when the ignition switch is in the ON position before starting the engine, we recommend that the system be checked by an authorized dealer.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

</resources>
